Guide to the Hot Peaches Records MSS.420
Fales Library and Special Collections
Hot Peaches Records
1950s-2014, undated
1971-1992
Fales Library and Special Collections
Camicia, Jimmy
MSS.420
23 Linear Feet in 33 manuscript boxes, 3 record cartons, 1 cassette box, 1 card box, 1 small flat box, 1 oversized flat box,1 flat-file folder and items in 2 shared boxes.
96.55 Gigabytes in 1,538 computer files.
62 videocassettes (vhs)
50 audiocassettes
2 sound tape reels
14 videocassettes (u-matic)
12 videoreels (1/2 inch)
Hot Peaches was a drag theater company founded in 1972 by writer and performer Jimmy Camicia. The group was known for their collaborative interactions with other drag performance groups and queer revolutionaries, including cast member Marsha P. Johnson. The group was based in New York City and performed shows regularly from the 1970s to the early 2000s not only in New York clubs, but also tours in Europe. Hot Peaches was often a platform for cast members' self-expression, as well as a nurturing queer community. The Hot Peaches Records contain material connected to their performances including scripts; press clippings; show production work books; digital and analog performance recordings; cast and performance photographs; and promotional announcements and posters. This collection also contains personal material created by Jimmy Camicia including school ephemera, writings, and journals dating from the late 1950s to 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Jimmy Camicia, 2014. The accession number associated with this gift is 2014.420.
Appraisal
The following were removed from the collection: 61 DVDs and CDs (either damaged or duplicates); 19 reference copy DVDs of analog recordings; 2 commercial VHS; approximately 100 rolled posters (duplicates/outside the collection's scope); unmarked commercial sheet music; and approximately 10 publications and books that had existing copies within the NYU library.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into four series. Each is arranged chronologically within.
Series I. Recordings
Series II. Scripts
Series III. Shows and Tours
Series IV. Jimmy Camicia Writings
Historical Note
Hot Peaches was a theater company working mostly in drag in New York City during the 1970s to the early 2000s. The company was founded by Jimmy Camicia in 1972, who befriended a group of drag queens in New York and was inspired to write shows for them to perform. Self-defined as as gay theater group, the Hot Peaches created shows that expressed the gay experience with a campy and political twist. Early shows were known for the castmembers' costumes, which often included vibrant, sparkling glam outfits with liberal use of platform boots, glitter, and feather boas. Camicia almost exclusively wrote the scripts, and the shows were put on three to five times per year at a variety of small theaters in Manhattan including Peach Pitts, Theater for the New City, La Mama, and Theater Genesis. The group would also occasionally do European tours, performing in England, Amsterdam, Scotland, Italy, and Germany, often providing their audiences with an experience that was not necessarily available for the gay communities in these countries. Notable cast members include the activist and performer Marsha P. Johnson, Sister Tooey, Wilhelmina Ross, Ian McKay, and Split Britches founder Peggy Shaw.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Some audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Access to some of the audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Scope and Contents
The Hot Peaches Records (1971-2014) include analog and digital recordings, and paper material related to Hot Peaches, a New York City-based gay theater group who based their shows on political camp and were dominated by drag performers. The Hot Peaches Records document the theater company's artistic processes, as well as the broader context of avant-garde musical performance, male and female gay performers, and queer communities in New York City in the late 20th century. Performance audio and video recordings in this collection date from the 1970s to the 2000s and include not only Hot Peaches shows, but also fundraisers to assist former castmates like International Chrysis and Ian McKay. The collection also includes photographs of the cast, performances, backstage, and images from their European tours. Publicity material includes fliers, postcards, posters, and press releases. Show production work books include notated scripts, cast lists, stage directions, press clippings, and photographs.
Drag shows; Drag queens; Artists and theater; Gay theater -- United States; Scripts (documents); Drag community; Gender identity in the theater; Musical theater -- New York (State) -- New York; Gay liberation movement -- United States.; Transgender people -- United States; Theatrical companies; Theatrical managers; Video recordings.; Audiocassettes.; Color photographs.; Musical theater; Diaries; Camicia, Jimmy; Hot Peaches; Johnson, Marsha P., 1945-1992; International Chrysis
- Series I. Recordings, 1971-2014; 5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, 1 cassette box, and 2 shared boxes.; 62 videocassettes (vhs); 50 audiocassettes; 2 sound tape reels; 14 videocassettes (u-matic); 12 videoreels (1/2 inch); 96.2 Gigabytes in 53 audio and video files
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes analog and digital recordings of Hot Peaches show performances, benefits, and readings dating from the early 1970s to the 2000s. Recordings in this series are a combination of shows performed in New York, including The Heat, Gay?, and Divas of Sheridan Square as well as European tour performances in London and Berlin including The Heat and Concentrated Camp. This series also contains the Marsha P Johnson documentary Pay It No Mind; video clips highlighting individual cast members; compilations of Hot Peaches shows; and the film Hot Peaches Retrospective, a documentary film containing interviews with the Jimmy Camicia, performance footage, and interviews with cast members. Recordings of Hot Peaches fundraisers to assistance friend in their community include footage for the Break a Leg Gala Benefit for Hot Peaches cast member Ian McKay in 1981, and Chrysis in Heels benefit for former cast member International Chrysis in 1990.
  - Hot Peaches Cast Member Miss Marie -- Show Footage Clips, 1970s-1980s; cuid39182 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_8)
  - Compilation -- The Magic Hype / Berlin / Angels / Jimmy Centola, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Vhs 420.035)
  - The Magic Hype Part I, October-November 1973 (Box 4, Half inch video reel 420.119)
  - The Magic Hype Part II, October-November 1973 (Box 4, Half inch video reel 420.118)
  - The Magic Hype Part III, October-November 1973 (Box 4, Half inch video reel 420.117)
  - The Magic Hype -- First Half, 1973; cuid39183 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_9)
  - The Demented Divas, May 1974 (Box 2, Vhs 420.086)
  - The Demented Divas Part I, May 1974 (Box 2, Half inch video reel 420.120)
  - The Demented Divas Part II, May 1974 (Box 2, Half inch video reel 420.121)
  - The Demented Divas Part III, May 1974 (Box 2, Half inch video reel 420.122)
  - Wizard of Oz Parade / Silver Dollar Party Gay Pride Day -- Compilation, July-August 1974; ID: 420.0014 (Box 4, Half inch video reel 420.0014)
  - The Divas of Sheridan Square, November-December 1975; ID: 420.0001 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0001)
  - The Divas of Sheridan Square, 1975; ID: 420.0019 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0019)
  - The Divas of Sheridan Square at St. Mark's on the Bowery, New York, 1975; cuid39184 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_10)
  - The Divas of Sheridan Square, New York City -- Part I, 1975; cuid39185 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_11)
  - The Divas of Sheridan Square, New York City -- Part I, 1975; cuid39186 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_12)
  - The Divas of Sheridan Square, New York City -- Part II, 1975; cuid39187 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_13)
  - Gay? Part I, 1977 (Box 4, Half inch video reel 420.114)
  - Gay? Part II, 1977 (Box 2, Half inch video reel 420.115)
  - Gay? Part III, 1977 (Box 4, Half inch video reel 420.116)
  - Gay?, 1977; cuid39175 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_1)
  - Gay? at Institute of Contemporary Arts, London, 1977; cuid39176 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_2)
  - Gay? at Institute of Contemporary Arts, London, 1977; cuid39177 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_3)
  - Side A: Songs from Gay? / Side B: Dutch Radio, 1977 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.124)
  - Compilation -- Rice Fine / Brothels / Bettes Interview / Gay?, 1977 (Box 1, Vhs 420.032)
  - Gay?, 1977 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.059)
  - Gay? -- Circus and Peg Leg, 1977 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.132)
  - Gay? -- Music, undated; cuid39181 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_7)
  - Side A: Gay? / Side B: Telling Tales, 1977 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.074)
  - Oscar, Boston, September 8, 1978 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.129)
  - Side A: Hot Peaches Variety / Side B: Jan's Music, 1978-1979 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.135)
  - An Evening with Sister Tooey at The Loft, 1979; cuid39188 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_14)
  - Break a Leg Gala Benefit for Ian McKay, May 25, 1981 (Box 2, Vhs 420.089)
  - Valentine's Party, February 14, 1982 (Box 2, Vhs 420.088)
  - Midnight Curtain, August 1982 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0020)
  - Musical Versions, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.070)
  - Waldorf Salad, January 1983 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.068)
  - Waldorf Salad, January 1983 (Box 2, Vhs 420.087)
  - Waldorf Salad, January 1983 (Box 2, Vhs 420.095)
  - Side A: Oscar / Side B: Gossip, 1983 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.067)
  - Compilation -- Away / Sam's Place / Joey in New York, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Vhs 420.034)
  - The Downtown Special #1, July 28, 1984 (Box 3, U-matic 420.111)
  - The Downtown Special #1, August 1984 (Box 3, U-matic 420.103)
  - The Downtown Special #1, August 1984 (Box 3, U-matic 420.104)
  - The Downtown Special #1, August 1984 (Box 1, Vhs 420.021)
  - Appetize the Beast, September 17, 1984 (Box Shared Fales 046, Quarter inch audio reel 420.139)
  - Harvest Moon Garden Party, September 30, 1984 (Box 2, Vhs 420.083)
  - The Downtown Special #2: X-Mas Cards, December 16, 1984 (Box 3, U-matic 420.100)
  - The Downtown Special #2: X-Mas Cards, December 16, 1984 (Box 3, U-matic 420.101)
  - The Downtown Special #2: X-Mas Cards, December 16, 1984 (Box 3, U-matic 420.102)
  - The Downtown Special #2: X-Mas Cards -- Promotional Spot, December 24, 1984 (Box 3, U-matic 420.098)
  - The Downtown Special #2: X-Mas Cards, December 1984 (Box 1, Vhs 420.022)
  - The Downtown Special #2: X-Mas Cards, December 1984 (Box 1, Vhs 420.031)
  - The Downtown Special #3: 1984, Revisited (Box 1, Vhs 420.023)
  - Island Music Only -- Bill Smith, 1984 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.078)
  - Finished Tracks -- Bill Smith, 1984 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.079)
  - Summer 84 -- Dog People and Others, 1984 (Box 2, Vhs 420.093)
  - Side A: Jimmy and Bill Smith / Side B: Tony Fish with Bill Smith Tracks, 1984, 1988 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.066)
  - The Downtown Special #3: 1984, Revisited, January 22, 1985 (Box 3, U-matic 420.109)
  - The Downtown Special #3: 1984, Revisited, January 1985 (Box 3, U-matic 420.110)
  - The Downtown Special #3: 1984, Revisited, January 1985 (Box 3, U-matic 420.108)
  - The Downtown Special #4: The Last Brunch -- Camera Master, April 8, 1985 (Box 3, U-matic 420.099)
  - The Downtown Special #4: The Last Brunch, April 1985 (Box 3, U-matic 420.106)
  - The Downtown Special #4: The Last Brunch, April 1985 (Box 3, U-matic 420.107)
  - The Downtown Special #4: The Last Brunch, April 1985 (Box 1, Vhs 420.024)
  - The Downtown Special #4: The Last Brunch -- Various Performances, April 1985 (Box 1, Vhs 420.030)
  - The Last Brunch at Theater for the New City, New York, April 1985; cuid39189 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_15)
  - Off the Cuff (Waldorf Salad Revival) Part II, October 26, 1985 (Box 2, Vhs 420.084)
  - Off the Cuff (Waldorf Salad Revival) Part III, October 27, 1985 (Box 2, Vhs 420.094)
  - Off the Cuff (Waldorf Salad Revival), October 1985 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.076)
  - Off the Cuff (Waldorf Salad Revival) -- Piano Accompaniment Only, October 1985 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.077)
  - International Chrysis at Boy Bar Demo and Shows, 1986-1989; ID: 420.0006 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0006)
  - Telling Tales (The Gay Book of the Dead), March 1987 (Box 2, Vhs 420.085)
  - Songs for Telling Tales (The Gay Book of the Dead) at Theater for a New City, 1987 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.075)
  - Concentrated Camp, February 7, 1988 (Box 2, Vhs 420.091)
  - The Heat, Last at Theater for the New City Performance -- International Chrysis Change, June 18, 1988; ID: 420.0003 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0003)
  - The Heat, June 18, 1988; ID: 420.0015 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0015)
  - The Heat, June 18, 1988; cuid39190 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_16)
  - The Heat at Women's Interart Theater Gay Day, June 26, 1988; ID: 420.0002 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0002)
  - The Heat at Theater for the New City, New York, June 1988; cuid39191 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_17)
  - The Heat, June 1988 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.073)
  - Harvest Moon Cabaret -- Original, November 12, 1988; ID: 420.0018 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0018)
  - Harvest Moon Cabaret Benefit for Concentrated Camp Tour, Soho Gallery, 1988; cuid39192 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_18)
  - Harvest Moon Cabaret Benefit for Concentrated Camp Tour, Soho Gallery, circa 1988; cuid39193 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_19)
  - The Heat Compilation -- Theater for the New City, New York (1988); Tempodrom, Berlin (1989); and Specks Film, Berlin (1989), 1988-1989; cuid39194 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_20)
  - Concentrated Camp, January 8, 1989 (Box 2, Vhs 420.080)
  - Club Performance at Don't Tell Mama, New York City, August 5, 1989; ID: 420.0004 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0004)
  - Hot Peaches at Tempodrom in Berlin, August 1989 (Box 2, Vhs 420.092)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp (European Tour), August 1989 (Box 1, Vhs 420.029)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp (European Tour), August-October 1989 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.072)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp (European Tour), and The Heat at Berlin Tempodrom, August-October 1989 (Box 2, Vhs 420.082)
  - Hot Peaches Live, September 27, 1989 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.053)
  - Hot Peaches Live, September 27, 1989 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.069)
  - Berlin Interview, 1989 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.071)
  - Chrysis Heels (Benefit) -- Rehearsal, February 1990; ID: 420.0012 (Box 1, Cd 420.0012)
  - Chrysis Heels (Benefit) -- Rehearsal and Backstage, February 1990; ID: 420.0016 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0016)
  - Chrysis Heels (Benefit) -- Rehearsal and Backstage, February 1990; ID: 420.0017 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0017)
  - Chrysis Heels (Benefit) -- Excerpts, February 20, 1990; ID: 420.0007 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0007)
  - Chrysis Heels (Benefit), February 20, 1990; ID: 420.0010 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0010)
  - Chrysis Heels Benefit at La Mama Club, February 20, 1990; cuid39195 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_21)
  - Chrysis Heels Benefit at La Mama Club -- Excerpts, February 20, 1990; cuid39196 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_22)
  - Chrysis Heels Benefit at La Mama Club -- Rehearsal, Backstage, Performance, February 20, 1990; cuid39197 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_23)
  - Chrysis Heels Benefit, La Mama Club -- Tony, February 20, 1990; cuid39198 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_24)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp (European Tour), and The Heat at the Schmidt, June 3, 1990 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.052)
  - Concentrated Camp, East Berlin, Summer 1990; cuid39199 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_25)
  - Concentrated Camp, East Berlin, Summer 1990; cuid39200 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_26)
  - Music from Concentrated Camp, Hamburg, Germany (European Tour), June 10, 1990 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.127)
  - Hamburg, Germany Encores (European Tour), July 7, 1990 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.126)
  - The Fall of the Wall Revue (European Tour), July 7, 1990 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.138)
  - Brief Encounters No. 1, 2, 3, September 12 and 19, 1990 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.051)
  - Harvest Moon Cabaret, November 24, 1990; ID: 420.0008 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0008)
  - Harvest Moon Ball at Theater for the New City, New York, November 24, 1990; cuid39201 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_27)
  - Harvest Moon Cabaret -- Duplicate, November 24, 1990; ID: 420.0009 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0009)
  - Dutch Interview, 1991 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.054)
  - The Hollywood Musical, # 3 and 4, 1991 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.056)
  - Joe Diary, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.057)
  - Side A: Christopher Street Columbus Music Only / Side B: Cabaret Fundraiser, March 1992 and April 1, 1992 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.130)
  - Christopher Street Columbus, May 30, 1992 (Box 2, Vhs 420.040)
  - Christopher Street Columbus, May 30, 1992 (Box 2, Vhs 420.041)
  - Christopher Street Columbus, May 30, 1992 (Box 2, Vhs 420.042)
  - Christopher Street Columbus, May 30, 1992 (Box 2, Vhs 420.043)
  - Christopher Street Columbus -- Performances New York City and Berlin, May-June 1992 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.055)
  - Hot Peaches in Berlin, June 1992 (Box 2, Vhs 420.090)
  - Split: Portrait of a Drag Queen, 1992 (Box 1, Vhs 420.028)
  - Split: Portrait of a Drag Queen, 1992; cuid39202 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_28)
  - Not Up to Snuff, August 20, 1993 (Box 2, Vhs 420.081)
  - Not Up to Snuff, September 12, 1993 (Box 2, Vhs 420.097)
  - Beyond Possessed (Not Up to Snuff Revival), September 9, 1994 (Box 1, Vhs 420.025)
  - Late Nite Indulgences -- Edited Version, at Theater for the New City, May-June 1996 (Box 1, Vhs 420.026)
  - Late Nite Indulgences -- Original, May-June 1996 (Box 1, Vhs 420.027)
  - Play Genet, November 23, 1997 (Box 2, Vhs 420.037)
  - Play Genet, November 23, 1997 (Box 2, Vhs 420.039)
  - Play Genet, November 23, 1997 (Box 2, Vhs 420.047)
  - Play Genet -- Music, Entire Show, 1997 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.061)
  - Play Genet, June, September 1998 (Box 2, Vhs 420.045)
  - Play Genet, September 25, 1998 (Box 2, Vhs 420.038)
  - Play Genet, September 25, 1998 (Box 2, Vhs 420.046)
  - Play Genet, September 25, 1998 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.065)
  - Play Genet -- Part 1, 1998 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.134)
  - Play Genet -- Part 2, 1997-1998 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.128)
  - Play Genet Songs -- Instrument Tracks Master, 1997-1998 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.137)
  - Compilation -- Hot Peaches in Hot Waters / Play Genet / TO! U All Have a Safe Trip!, 1998 (Box 2, Vhs 420.044)
  - Side A: Xmas / Side B: Play Genet, Part IV, 1998 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.131)
  - Peaches in Parts -- Documentary on Hot Peaches, circa 1998; cuid39203 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_29)
  - Hot Peaches Film 1973, Hot Peaches Retrospective (1973-1998), circa 1998; cuid39204 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_30)
  - 1974 Hot Peaches Film, circa 1998; cuid39205 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_31)
  - Nite: Scat Queen of Atlanta, July 9, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.060)
  - Play Genet -- Edit, October 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.123)
  - Studio Instrumental Tracks I, December 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.064)
  - Session Studio I, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.063)
  - Session Studio II, January 26, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.062)
  - Margie Reading, February 27, 2001 (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.036)
  - Tulips and Cadavers -- Reading, 2004 (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.136)
  - Entr'Acte -- Meeting, Script Reading, May 27, 2009; cuid39206 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_32)
  - The Tony Fish Show, July 12, 2009; cuid39207 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_33)
  - Individual Cast Member Highlights -- Hot Peaches Les Boys, Hot Peaches Our Queens, and Hot Peach Women, October 19, 2009; cuid39208 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_34)
  - Movie -- Pay It No Mind: Marsha P. Johnson -- Screening at IFC Cinema, Pre-Show Interviews, November 28, 2011; cuid39209 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_35)
  - Movie -- Pay It No Mind: Marsha P. Johnson, circa 2011; cuid39210 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_36)
  - Movie --Pay It No Mind: Marsha P. Johnson -- 1992 Marsha P. Johnson and Hot Peaches Cast Member Interviews Used in Film, circa 2011; cuid39211 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_37)
  - Hot Peaches Cast Members -- Photograph Video Montages, February 2014; cuid39212 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_38)
  - Hot Peaches Cast Member Wilhelmina Ross -- Still Photographs and Show Video Clips, undated; cuid39213 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_39)
  - "Brothers -- Jim, Joe Pete" -- Apartment Interior Footage, undated; cuid39214 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_40)
  - Compilation -- Video Follies #1 and Camp Music and Close Ups, Undated; ID: 420.0005 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0005)
  - Hot Peaches Film, Undated (Box 1, Vhs 420.033)
  - Song for The Heat, Undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.048)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp, Undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.049)
  - No Secrets, Undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.050)
  - Jan's Version of Banking on the Lord, Undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.058)
  - Jan's Version of Anonymously Yours, Undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.058)
  - Through the Years, 1946-1996, Tommy and Flo, Undated (Box 2, Vhs 420.096)
  - Hot Peaches Master Tape, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 420.105)
  - Hot Peaches Retrospective Parts I-IV, Undated; ID: 420.0013 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0013)
  - Poems, Undated (Box 4, Half inch video reel 420.112)
  - Poems, Undated (Box 4, Half inch video reel 420.113)
  - Play Genet -- Music Only, Undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 420.125)
  - Cool Jazz, Undated (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 420.133)
  - "Gay and in the '70s" -- Music from Unknown Show, undated; cuid39178 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_4)
  - "The Girls", undated; cuid39179 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_5)
  - Hot Peaches '80s Music -- Unknown Show, undated; cuid39180 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_6)